quantum-confidence.com 2017-12-13

# Quantum Confidence With The Morry MethodTh

**Privacy Policy  
**  
Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy   
policy tells you how we use personal information   
collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy   
before using the site or submitting any personal   
information. By using the site, you are accepting the   
practices described in this privacy policy. These   
practices may be changed, but any changes will be   
posted and changes will only apply to activities and   
information on a going forward, not retroactive basis.   
You are encouraged to review the privacy policy   
whenever you visit the site to make sure that you   
understand how any personal information you provide   
will be used.

Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy   
policy is for this web site only. If you link to other   
web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at   
those sites.

**Collection of Information  
**We collect personally identifiable information, like   
names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when   
voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information   
you provide is used to fulfill you specific request.   
This information is only used to fulfill your specific   
request to add you to our mailing list so you may be   
updated with respect to our products as necessary.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology  
**The site may use cookie and tracking technology   
depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking   
technology is useful for gathering information such as   
browser type and operating system, tracking the number   
of visitors to the website, and understanding how visitors   
use the site. Cookies can also help customize the site   
for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected   
via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if   
you previously provided personally identifiable   
information, cookies may be tied to such information.   
Aggregate cookie and tracking information will not be   
shared with third parties.

**Distribution of Information  
**We may share information with governmental agencies or   
other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or   
investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or   
required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or   
prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized   
transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has   
already taken place. The information is not provided to   
these companies for marketing purposes. 

**Commitment to Data Security  
**Your personally identifiable information is kept   
secure. Only authorized employees, agents and   
contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure   
and confidential) have access to this information. All   
emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt   
out of further mailings. 

**Privacy Contact Information  
**If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about   
our privacy policy you may contact us using the   
information below:

By e-mail: support@quantum-mind-power.com  
By Phone: 416-876-7939

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. 

Any changes to this policy will be posted.

**Return Policy  
**  
In order to return QMP for refund, this is what you need   
to do...

You simply need to send the CD's, manual and case   
(original packaging) back to the shipper. This   
information is on the packaging that the CD's originally  
arrived to you in.

If you no longer have the packaging, here is the address   
to send it back to..

Corporate Disk Company  
4610 Prime Parkway  
McHenry, Illinois. 60050  
USA

Attention: TMM REFUND

* Please make sure you include the words "Attention:   
TMM REFUND" just below the address on the front of the   
package.

* Remember to include your name and address and   
receipt/purchase number so we can trace the order and   
refund you promptly.

* The CD's and original package must be shipped back in   
suitably padded packaging in order to protect them during   
the shipping process.

**Shipping and Handling/Delivery Information  
**  
We deliver worldwide via UPS.

Please allow between 1-4 weeks for your order to arrive,   
(this is calculated from the date of shipping which is   
normally the next business day after you place your   
order).

Shipping and handling costs will normally vary between   
$18 for orders shipped within North American and $35 for   
orders shipped Internationally.

**General Contact Information  
**If you have any questions, concerns, or comments regarding  
any of our policies or procedures you may feel free to   
contact us using the following information:

By e-mail: support@quantum-mind-power.com  
By Phone: 416-876-7939

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. 

Any changes to this policy will be posted.
